Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - P-S
        - Siete Potencias - Smokin', 1976; SR-27680; Siete Potencias (Box 67)
          Catalog # TR-126X; A-side Matrix # 7 PONTCIAS A TR-126-A
          TR Records
        - Side Effect - Rainbow visions, 1978; SR-27681; Side Effect (Box 67)
          Catalog # F-9569; A-side Matrix # F-9569-A
        - Sigler, Bunny - Let it snow, 1980; SR-27682; Sigler, Bunny (Box 67)
          Catalog # SA 8531 DJ; A-side Matrix # D SA-8531-A
        - Silk - Midnight dancer, 1979; SR-27683; Silk (Box 67)
          Catalog # AL 36025; A-side Matrix # AL-36025 2B
        - Silken - Gizmo, 2000; SR-27684; Silken (Box 67)
          Catalog # FB 003; A-side Matrix # Tim D FB003-A
          Functional Breaks
          Exeter, United Kingdom
        - Silver Bullet - Bring forth the guillotine, 1989; SR-27685; Silver Bullet (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27686. Different discs.
          Catalog # TTT 008; A-side Matrix # LYN 22966 TTT 0008 A1 JA
          Tam Tam Records
        - Silver Bullet - 20 seconds to comply, 1989; SR-27686; Silver Bullet (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27685. Different discs.
          Catalog # TTT 019; A-side Matrix # LYN 24466 TTT 019 A1 JA
        - Silver, Karen - Hold on I'm comin', 1979; SR-27687; Silver, Karen (Box 67)
          Catalog # CP-707; A-side Matrix # T CP-SA-CT1 707
        - Silver Platinum - Silver Platinum, 1981; SR-27688; Silver Platinum (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27689. Different discs.
          Catalog # SW 70002; A-side Matrix # SW-1-70002-G5 #2
        - Silver Platinum - Dance, 1980; SR-27689; Silver Platinum (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27688. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPRO-00010(DJ); A-side Matrix # V LEMAY SR1-00010 DJ G-1
        - Silver Flash Funk - Funky space player (supermix), 1983; SR-27690; Silver Flash Funk (Box 67)
          Catalog # SF002; A-side Matrix # SF-002-A
          Silver Flash Funk Records, Inc.
        - Simon, Carly - The best of Carly Simon, 1977; SR-27691; Simon, Carly (Box 67)
          Catalog # 6E-109; A-side Matrix # SP 6E-109-A-10
        - Simon, Carly - Anticipation, 1971; SR-27692; Simon, Carly (Box 67)
          Catalog # EKS-75016; A-side Matrix # EKS 75016-A-13-SP ESRTD 5-7-76
        - Simon, Joe - Happy birthday, baby, 1979; SR-27693; Simon, Joe (Box 67)
          Catalog # SP-1-6724; A-side Matrix # FW C6 SP-1-6724-AS-CP1
          Spring Records
        - Simon, Joe - Going through these changes, 1978; SR-27694; Simon, Joe (Box 67)
          Catalog # PRO 081; A-side Matrix # PRO 08178NP 3905-5-CD-1 K-10443 GOL
        - Simón Orchestra - Mr. Big Shot, 1979; SR-27695; Simón Orchestra (Box 67)
          Catalog # PD-1-6216; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6216-AS-CP-1
        - Simone, Francie - Let your body run, 1979; SR-27696; Simone, Francie (Box 67)
          Catalog # BC 4001; A-side Matrix # B&C-4001-A -2-
          BC Records
        - Simple Minds - Sons and fascination, 1981; SR-27697; Simple Minds (Box 67)
          Catalog # V 2207; A-side Matrix # V 2207-A-2 COURAGE OF DREAMS BUBO TA1YE
        - Simple Minds - New gold dream (81-82-83-84), 1982; SR-27698; Simple Minds (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27699. Different discs.
          Catalog # V 2230; A-side Matrix # V 2230 A 2 HEDGEHOGS
        - Simple Minds - Promised you a miracle, 1983; SR-27699; Simple Minds (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27698. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-17223; A-side Matrix # AM SP 017223-A ES2 EMW
        - Simply Red - Men and women, 1987; SR-27700; Simply Red (Box 67)
          Catalog # 60727-1; A-side Matrix # STE 60727 A 4 DMM STERLING 2-2
        - Paul Simpson Connection - Treat her sweeter, 1985; SR-27701; Paul Simpson Connection (Box 67)
          Catalog # EZS-7517; A-side Matrix # LOVE TO TAM AND CATS EZS-7517-A
          Easy Street Records
        - Simpson, Ray - Tiger love, 1978; SR-27702; Simpson, Ray (Box 67)
          Catalog # BSK 3180; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3180-RE2 JW1
        - Simpson, Valerie - Keep it comin', 1977; SR-27703; Simpson, Valerie (Box 67)
          Catalog # T6-351S1; A-side Matrix # T6-351S1-2665-S-06D #13 21934 GZ
        - Sims, Joyce - Come into my life, 1987; SR-27704; Sims, Joyce (Box 67)
          Catalog # TLX-10X; A-side Matrix # TLX-10-X-DMM SP-0-1 EDPN11SF1 SM1 MASTERDISK DMM
          Sleeping Bag Records
        - Singh, Talvin - Anokha (soundz of the Asian Undeground) (disc one), 1997; SR-27705; Singh, Talvin (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27706. Double album.
          Catalog # MLPSD 1120; A-side Matrix # MLPSD 1120/524341-1 A2 THE EXCHANGE-NILZ
        - Singh, Talvin - Anokha (soundz of the Asian Undeground) (disc two), 1997; SR-27706; Singh, Talvin (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27705. Double album.
          Catalog # MLPSD 1120; A-side Matrix # MLPSD 1120/524341-1 C1 THE EXCHANGE-NILZ
        - Singing Francine - Flying high with Singing Francine, 1977; SR-27707; Singing Francine (Box 67)
          Catalog # GS 7787; A-side Matrix # GS 7787 A
        - Singleton, Charlie - Man on a mission, 1989; SR-27708; Singleton, Charlie (Box 67)
          Catalog # AL 44320; A-side Matrix # AL 44320-3A G1 Skinner EUROPA P1 SK A4
        - Singleton, Maxine - Don't you love it, 1982; SR-27709; Singleton, Maxine (Box 68)
          Catalog # TAS-2801E; A-side Matrix # TAS-2801-E-A HERBIE
          Peter Pan Artists Series
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Seminar, 1989; SR-27710; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 68)
          Catalog # NMR 70150; A-side Matrix # NMR-70150-A G-1 S-22561
          Nastymix Records
          Seattle, Washington
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Swass, 1988; SR-27711; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 68)
          Catalog # NMR 70123; A-side Matrix # NMR-7-0123-A-RE1 19129 R2 M'M
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Chief boot knocka, 1994; SR-27712; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 68)
          Catalog # 9 45540-1; A-side Matrix # 1-45540-A-SR1 DMM 1-1 SP-PRM RB Preusion
          American Recordings
        - Sisqo - Thong song, 2000; SR-27713; Sisqo (Box 68)
          Catalog # SONG 1; A-side Matrix # FSV SONG 1 A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Sister Nancy - One, two, 1982; SR-27714; Sister Nancy (Box 68)
          Catalog # WR 1990; A-side Matrix # WR 1990 A
          Techniques
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Sister Sledge - All American girls, 1981; SR-27715; Sister Sledge (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27716. Different discs.
          Catalog # SD 16027; A-side Matrix # SP 0-1 SM4-2 ST-CTN-804633-A RL
        - Sister Sledge - All American girls, 1981; SR-27716; Sister Sledge (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27715. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 256; A-side Matrix # 1-1 ST-DM-39316-2 RL SP
          Cotillion
        - Sister Sledge - Love somebody today, 1980; SR-27717; Sister Sledge (Box 68)
          Catalog # SD 16012; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-804433-C SP FW SG
        - Sister Sledge - We are family, 1979; SR-27718; Sister Sledge (Box 68)
          Catalog # SD 5209; A-side Matrix # ATLANTIC-LPS-2002530-A Cltouer
        - Sister Souljah - 360 Degrees of power, 1992; SR-27719; Sister Souljah (Box 68)
          Catalog # E 48713; A-side Matrix # AL 48713-2 F/W CSB FF
        - Sisterhood - Gift, 1986; SR-27720; Sisterhood (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27721. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SIS 020; A-side Matrix # A GIFT FROM THE RASPBERRY REICH MPO SIS 020 A1 VERYRIDIGUNGSKRIEG
          Merciful Release
        - Sisterhood - Gift, 1986; SR-27721; Sisterhood (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27720. 2 copies.
        - Skah Shah #1 de New York - On the move, 1983; SR-27722; Skah Shah #1 de New York (Box 68)
          Catalog # JD 1839-2; A-side Matrix # 1839-A3 -10
          JD Productions
        - Skah Shah #1 de New York - Nou-la-dial #1, 1984; SR-27723; Skah Shah #1 de New York (Box 68)
          Catalog # JD-1839-6; A-side Matrix # JD-1839-6A
        - Skeme Team - Plan-a, 1999; SR-27724; Skeme Team (Box 68)
          Catalog # T21LP1042; A-side Matrix # PA 11/98 T21LP-1042-A
          3-2-1 Records
        - Skinny Boys - Skinny & proud, 1987; SR-27725; Skinny Boys (Box 68)
          Catalog # 1077-1-J; A-side Matrix # 1077-1-J A Emw CSB FF
        - Skip Mahoaney & The Casuals - Running away from love, 1976; SR-27726; Skip Mahoaney & The Casuals (Box 68)
          Catalog # 69471; A-side Matrix # ABET-69471-A F/W
          Abet
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - Skipworth and Turner - Skipworth and Turner, 1986; SR-27727; Skipworth and Turner (Box 68)
          Catalog # 1-25434; A-side Matrix # 1-25434-A-SH2 HERBIE JR B-24448-SH2 13390 1-
        - Skowa e a Máfia - La famiglia, 1989; SR-27728; Skowa e a Máfia (Box 68)
          Catalog # 064 792699 1; A-side Matrix # 792 699 1 01 1989 ERbCK ERbCK ERbCK 200
          Brazil
        - Skull Snaps - Skull Snaps, 1995; SR-27729; Skull Snaps (Box 68)
          Catalog # CPLP 8094; A-side Matrix # CPLP 8094 A1 2 DAMONT A
          Charly Records
        - Sky Cutter - Blue notes; Lost, 1996; SR-27755; Sky Cutter (Box 68)
          Catalog # BLOOD 3; A-side Matrix # BLOOD 3A-1
          Blood Records
        - Skyy - Call me, 1981; SR-27730; Skyy (Box 68)
          Catalog # SG 356; A-side Matrix # SG-356A-1
        - Slave - Just a touch of love, 1979; SR-27731; Slave (Box 68)
          Catalog # SD 5217; A-side Matrix # ST CTN 794353 B 0-1 PR SP
        - Slave - Bad enuff, 1983; SR-27732; Slave (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27733. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 90118-1; A-side Matrix # E-1 ST-CTN-835283-C
        - Slave - Bad enuff, 1983; SR-27733; Slave (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27732. 2 copies.
        - Slave - Show time, 1981; SR-27734; Slave (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27735; SR-27336. Different discs.
          Catalog # SD 5227; A-side Matrix # ST CTN 814769 G MLSF1 SM1
        - Slave - Wait for me, 1981; SR-27735; Slave (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27734; SR-27736. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 305; A-side Matrix # ST DM 40280-2
        - Slave - Snap shot, 1981; SR-27736; Slave (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27734; SR-27735. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 289; A-side Matrix # STDM 40285-1 1-1
        - Sleepy C - Phunk you, I like it, 1998; SR-27737; Sleepy C (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27738. Different discs.
          Catalog # PAE-011; A-side Matrix # PAE 011-A AVC NSC MADE IN CANADA
          Psychoactive
        - Faline, Tony - Break down, 1998; SR-27738; Faline, Tony (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27737. Different discs.
          Catalog # UN005; A-side Matrix # UNION 005-9804X02 A A2 SP6
          Union Records
        - Slim - Good to go, 1984; SR-27739; Slim (Box 68)
          Catalog # TDE-3002; A-side Matrix # TDE-3002-A F/WNS
          T.T.E.D. Records
        - Slow Children - Spring in Fialta, 1981; SR-27740; Slow Children (Box 68)
          Catalog # JD-12365; A-side Matrix # A1 C jd 12365 A
          Ensign
        - Slow Children - Vanessa vacillating, 1982; SR-27741; Slow Children (Box 68)
          Catalog # JD-13367; A-side Matrix # A1 A PD-13367A-1
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Dance to the music (medley), 1998; SR-27742; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 68)
          Catalog # TD-803; A-side Matrix # TD 803-A
          T.D. Records, Inc.
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Ain't but the one way, 1982; SR-27743; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 68)
          Catalog # 1-23700; A-side Matrix # B-16872-SH1 1-23700-A-SH1 SLM + 1874
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Greatest hits, 1970; SR-27744; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 68)
          Catalog # KE 30325; A-side Matrix # P AL 30325-3A
        - Sly Stone - Ten years too soon, 1979; SR-27745; Sly Stone (Box 68)
          Catalog # JE 35974; A-side Matrix # AL-35974-1A
        - Sly Stone - Seventh son (63/67), 2002; SR-27746; Sly Stone (Box 68)
          Catalog # VAMPI 003; A-side Matrix # AE 43467/A
          Vampi Soul
        - Smith, Dick - Initial thrust, 1983; SR-27747; Smith, Dick (Box 68)
          Catalog # 1-23835; A-side Matrix # B-17887 1 23835 SH1 A SLM 4005-X 1-1
        - Smith, Michael - Mi cyaan believe it, 1982; SR-27748; Smith, Michael (Box 68)
          Catalog # 6313 430; A-side Matrix # 012 6 313430 1 380 POLYGRAM A5
          Phonogram
        - Smith, Richard Jon - Stay with me tonight, 1982; SR-27749; Smith, Richard Jon (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27749. Different discs. Test pressing
          Catalog # JIVE T 10; A-side Matrix # BIBO TAPEOie JIVE T-10-A2
        - Smith, Richard Jon - Stay with me tonight, 1982; SR-27750; Smith, Richard Jon (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27750. Different discs.
          Catalog # VJ 12001; A-side Matrix # 1 T VS 12001 SA CT 2
        - Smith, Will - Born to reign (disc one), 2002; SR-27751; Smith, Will (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27752. Double album.
          Catalog # C2 86189; A-side Matrix # OASIS BL 86702-1A Obgs X1
        - Smith, Will - Born to reign (disc two), 2002; SR-27752; Smith, Will (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27751. Double album.
          Catalog # C2 86189; A-side Matrix # OASIS BL 86703-1A Obgs X1
        - Smithee, Alan - Blue blackness, 2003; SR-27753; Smithee, Alan (Box 68)
          Catalog # ULTLEG-02; A-side Matrix # ULTLEG-02-A F/W GSV
          Sounds Like Ultra
          Toronto, Ontario
        - Snapp - The Snapp, 1986; SR-27754; Snapp (Box 68)
          Catalog # BLU 704; A-side Matrix # BLU-704-A 45461 R1-
          Blue Heron Records
        - S.O. Project - Direct dizko, 1999; SR-27756; S.O. Project (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27757. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WR 015; A-side Matrix # 08 42587 20 1A1 WR-015
          Waves Records
        - S.O. Project - Direct dizko, 1999; SR-27757; S.O. Project (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27756. 2 copies.
        - Soccio, Gino - S-beat, 1980; SR-27758; Soccio, Gino (Box 68)
          Catalog # RFC 3430; A-side Matrix # RFC-1-3430-LW1
        - Soccio, Gino - Closer, 1981; SR-27759; Soccio, Gino (Box 68)
          Catalog # SD 16042; A-side Matrix # ST-RFC-8146 88-D 0-1 SM1-6 SP
        - Society - Yes 'n' deed, 1994; SR-27760; Society (Box 68)
          Catalog # PR-499-1; A-side Matrix # GR-499-1-A IN GOD WE TRUST MT
          Luke Records
        - Soft Cell - The art of falling apart, 1983; SR-27761; Soft Cell (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27762. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1-23769; A-side Matrix # 1-23769-A RE1 SR1 1-1
          Sire
        - Soft Cell - The art of falling apart, 1983; SR-27762; Soft Cell (Box 68)
          In same jacket as # SR-27761. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1-23769; A-side Matrix # 1-23769-C- RE1 SR1 1-1
        - Softones - Together, 1979; SR-27763; Softones; First Class (Box 68)
          Catalog # PA 1001; A-side Matrix # PA-1001-A FWO
          Park-Way International Records
        - Soirée - Soirée, 1979; SR-27764; Soirée (Box 68)
          Catalog # BXL1-3401; A-side Matrix # BXL-1-3401-A 1 A2C
          Roadshow
        - Solanke, Jimi - America's got magic, 1979; SR-27765; Solanke, Jimi (Box 68)
          Catalog # MD9034; A-side Matrix # MD 9034 A
          Makossa International Records
        - Solar Heat - Solar heat, 1979; SR-27766; Solar Heat (Box 68)
          Catalog # AA-1129; A-side Matrix # 15 AA-1129-A
        - Solid Ground - Relegation dogfight EP, 1997; SR-27767; Solid Ground (Box 68)
          Catalog # HAND045T; A-side Matrix # HAND 045T A-1-1-1 PDVL CJT2-
        - Solid Ground - The whole deal EP, 1997; SR-27768; Solid Ground (Box 69)
          Catalog # HAND 044T; A-side Matrix # HAND 044 T-AA1 PDVL PORKYS
        - Solo Harmonites Steel Orchestra - How you sweet so!, 1975; SR-27769; Solo Harmonites Steel Orchestra (Box 69)
          Catalog # RA 5052; A-side Matrix # RA 5052 A-1
          Ra
          Trinidad and Tobago
        - Sommer, Bert - Bert Sommer, 1970; SR-27770; Sommer, Bert (Box 69)
          Catalog # BDS 5082 A; A-side Matrix # BDS 5082 A-2 SON
        - Son of Sam - 1.K.B.P.M, 1987; SR-27771; Son of Sam (Box 69)
          Catalog # IRA 1; A-side Matrix # PROFANE 27 A2 IRA-1-A FILTHY LVCRE
          Rouska
          Bethlehem, Pennsylvania
        - Sonny & Cher - Sonny & Cher live, 1973; SR-27772; Sonny & Cher (Box 69)
          Catalog # MCA-2009; A-side Matrix # KRS 5554 A E1 4 1
        - Sono Tab - Audio graphics, 1997; SR-27773; Sono Tab (Box 69)
          Catalog # MUELLER2005; A-side Matrix # MÜLLER 2005 A D+M
          Müller Records
        - Sono Tab - Audio graphics, 1997; SR-27774; Sono Tab (Box 69)
        - Sonora Ponceña - New heights, 1980; SR-27775; Sonora Ponceña (Box 69)
          Catalog # JMIS 1074; A-side Matrix # JMIS-1074-A
          Inca Records
        - Sons of Robin Stone - I need it bad, 1982; SR-27776; Sons of Robin Stone (Box 69)
          Catalog # P-111; A-side Matrix # T-111-DJ
          Pezza Records
          Collingdale, Pennsylvania
        - Sophisticated Four - Check it out, 1997; SR-27777; Sophisticated Four (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27778. Different discs.
          Catalog # MBB-12-532; A-side Matrix # FW/O BBS-1100 A-RE-1-1 ae Brown PRC
          Mayhew Records
        - Sophisticated Four - Check it out, 1997; SR-27778; Sophisticated Four (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27777. Different discs.
          Catalog # F.J.-77; A-side Matrix # FW/S FJ 77 A-1 ae/Brown
        - Soraya - Soraya, 1978; SR-27779; Soraya (Box 69)
          Catalog # EPC 83421; A-side Matrix # 000 7811 EPC 83421 A1
        - S.O.S. Band - Sands of time, 1986; SR-27780; S.O.S. Band (Box 69)
          Catalog # Z 40279; A-side Matrix # PAL-40279-1C G1
          Tabu Records
        - S.O.S. Band - You, 1981; SR-27781; S.O.S. Band (Box 69)
          Catalog # AS 1310; A-side Matrix # XSS-168329-1C
        - S.O.S. Band - For you love, 1983; SR-27782; S.O.S. Band (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27783. Different discs.
          Catalog # AS 1817; A-side Matrix # XSS-169565-1A
        - S.O.S. Band - For you love (extended version), 1983; SR-27783; S.O.S. Band (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27782. Different discs.
          Catalog # 4Z9 04991; A-side Matrix # P C 429-04991-4AA 1
        - S.O.S. Band - The S.O.S. Band 1980-1987: the hit mixes, 1987; SR-27784; S.O.S. Band (Box 69)
          Catalog # 460189 1; A-side Matrix # 4601891 A1
        - S.O.S. Band - On the rise, 1983; SR-27785; S.O.S. Band (Box 69)
          Catalog # FZ 38697; A-side Matrix # P PAL-38697-1F
        - S.O.S. Band - You, 1981; SR-27786; S.O.S. Band (Box 69)
          Catalog # AS 1310; A-side Matrix # XSS-168328-1 H
        - S.O.S. Band - High hopes; Good & plenty, 1982; SR-27787; S.O.S. Band (Box 69)
          Catalog # 4Z9 03249; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-03249-3AB
        - SoSo - Dance mother, 1997; SR-27788; SoSo (Box 69)
          Catalog # UN 002; A-side Matrix # 9709X27-A ARD
        - Soul II Soul - Vol. II (1990- a new decade), 1990; SR-27789; Soul II Soul (Box 69)
          Catalog # DIX 90; A-side Matrix # DIX 90 A-1U-1-1 JA
          10 Records
        - Soul II Soul - Keep on movin', 1996; SR-27790; Soul II Soul (Box 69)
          Catalog # VST1612; A-side Matrix # VST 1612 A-02-01-01
        - Soul For Real - For life…, 1996; SR-27791; Soul For Real (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27792. 2 copies.
          Catalog # UPT-53012; A-side Matrix # UPT-53012-A HFM 96 CG
          Uptown Records
        - Soul For Real - For life…, 1996; SR-27792; Soul For Real (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27791. 2 copies.
        - Soul Patrol - Trippin' out, 1997; SR-27793; Soul Patrol; DJ Xtravagant (Box 69)
          Catalog # BR 02; A-side Matrix # BR-02-A time for Bryan Pogdwwk Rex It's All Good In The Hood! 2 times 2 no emia for the vocals DJ-X-MAVAGANT-is blowing up BOOYA --- AND I MEAN THAT, PLAY HATERS
          Booya Records
        - Soul Providers - Gimme the paw, 1997; SR-27794; Soul Providers; Fields, Lee (Box 69)
          Catalog # LP-008; A-side Matrix # LP-008-A
          Pure Records
        - Soul Rebellion - Simple rhythm, 1990; SR-27795; Soul Rebellion (Box 69)
          Catalog # 3-4002-0-DJ; A-side Matrix # 3-4002-0-A
          Cardiac Records
        - Soul Sounds - The best of the soul hits, 1969; SR-27796; Soul Sounds (Box 69)
          Catalog # SUS-5249; A-side Matrix # SUS-5249-1 (2)
          Sunset Records
        - Soul Train Gang - The Soul Train Gang, 1976; SR-27797; Soul Train Gang (Box 69)
          Catalog # BVL1-1844; A-side Matrix # A2 BVL1 1844A 1S
        - Southroad Connection - Ain't no time to sit down, 1979; SR-27798; Southroad Connection (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27799. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LT-997; A-side Matrix # FW O AD 00 LT-997-1
          United Artists Records
        - Southroad Connection - Ain't no time to sit down, 1979; SR-27799; Southroad Connection (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27798. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LT-997; A-side Matrix # FW O 00 LT-997-1
        - Southside Movement - Moving south, 1975; SR-27800; Southside Movement (Box 69)
          Catalog # T-485; A-side Matrix # M-485-AS 1B -wcm A2
          20th Century Records
        - Space Cadets - Space Cadets, 1981; SR-27801; Space Cadets (Box 69)
          Catalog # VSD 79442; A-side Matrix # VSD-79442-A N13273 COL AA
        - Space Needle - The moray eels eat the space needle (disc one), 1997; SR-27802; Space Needle (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27803. Double album.
          Catalog # ZER LP 2080; A-side Matrix # ZH-2080 A S-34534 mcnds
        - Space Needle - The moray eels eat the space needle (disc two), 1997; SR-27803; Space Needle (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27802. Double album.
          Catalog # ZER LP 2080; A-side Matrix # mcnds S-34534 ZH-2080 C
        - Space Project - Disco from another galaxy, 1978; SR-27804; Space Project (Box 69)
          Catalog # APL1-2853; A-side Matrix # APL1-2853A-1
        - Spagna - You are my energy, 1988; SR-27805; Spagna (Box 69)
          Catalog # CBS 463072 1; A-side Matrix # 01 463072 2A1
          CBS
        - Spain, Joanne - Elevator, 1976; SR-27806; Spain, Joanne (Box 69)
          Catalog # GRT-077; A-side Matrix # GRT-077-4454-DISCO MASTERFONICS G2T
          Casino Records
        - Spanish Prince - Dance, everybody, dance; Maria, 1987; SR-27807; Spanish Prince (Box 69)
          Catalog # BWAY-442; A-side Matrix # A-1 BWAY 442-A HW
        - Sparks - Whomp that sucker, 1981; SR-27808; Sparks (Box 69)
          Catalog # AFL1-4091; A-side Matrix # AJ B JA AFL1-4091A-1
        - Sparky-D - This is Sparky-D's world, 1988; SR-27809; Sparky-D; Grand Creator K-Wiz (Box 69)
          Catalog # BB 5-1088; A-side Matrix # BB-5-10-88-A DCHARLES
          B-Boy Records
          Bronx, New York
        - Sparrow - Vanessa, 1984; SR-27810; Sparrow; Mighty Sparrow (Box 69)
          Catalog # BSR-SP-024; A-side Matrix # BSR-SP-024-A JR
        - Sparrow - 25th Anniversary (disc one), 1980; SR-27811; Sparrow; Mighty Sparrow (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27813. Double album.
          Catalog # JAF 001; A-side Matrix # JAF-001-A FWO
        - Sparrow - 25th Anniversary (disc two), 1980; SR-27812; Sparrow; Mighty Sparrow (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27812. Double album.
          Catalog # JAF 001; A-side Matrix # JAF 001 C FWO
        - Sparrow - Sanford soca disco human rights, 1981; SR-27813; Sparrow; Mighty Sparrow (Box 69)
          Catalog # JAF 1004; A-side Matrix # FWO JAF 1004 B-